(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
The concert will be starting soon.
AZKi SOLO LIVE 2025 "Departure"
2025.11.19 PIA ARENA MM
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: To our guests
照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights.
声出し応援 OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
ライブグッズ 2次販売決定!!
Live merchandise 2nd round sale confirmed!!
11.19 公演終了後〜
Starting after the 11/19 performance.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
ライブグッズ 2次販売決定!!
11.19公演終了後〜
Live goods second wave sale decided!!
From after the 11.19 performance~
アニメにハマって、歌いたくなっちゃった。
I got into anime and wanted to sing.
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて...
Being able to sing karaoke while watching my favorite scenes...
尊すぎて、辛い！
It's so precious, it hurts!
歌いたいアニメ・ゲーミングソング見つけよう！
Let's find the anime and gaming songs you want to sing!
ねぇ、今日はどこ行く？
Hey, where should we go today?
Yahoo!カーナビ『推しドラ』好評販売中！
Yahoo! Car Nav 'Oshidora' is now on sale!
今なら両方購入で、ぺこあず限定ボイスも聞けちゃう。
Buy both now and you can also hear the exclusive Peko-Azu voice lines!
AZKiと一緒に、ドライブしよう！
Let's go for a drive with AZKi!
AZKi holoplus JACK
ホロプラス ジャック中 【本日22:00まで】
Currently jacking holoplus [Until 10:00 PM today]
ライブグッズ 2次販売決定!!
11.19 公演終了後〜
Live Goods: Second round of sales confirmed!!
Starting after the 11.19 performance
AZKi SOLO LiVE 2025 "Departure"
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
2025.11.19 PIA ARENA MM
Attention
ご来場のお客様へ
To all attendees
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is ok.
ライブグッズ2次販売決定!!
Live Goods 2nd Sale Decided!!
11.19 公演終了後〜
11.19 After the performance~
AZKi SOLO LiVE 2025 "Departure"
AZKi SOLO LiVE 2025 "Departure" 寄せ書き
Fan Messages for AZKi SOLO LiVE 2025 "Departure"
AZKi SOLO LiVE 2025 "Departure"
2025.11.19 WED PIA ARENA MM
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention
ご来場のお客様へ
To All Attendees
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights
during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
ライブグッズ 2次販売決定!!
11.19 公演終了後〜
Live Goods 2nd Sale Confirmed!!
Starting after the 11.19 performance~
本日は AZKi SOLO LiVE 2025 ＂Departure＂ に
Thank you for coming to AZKi SOLO LiVE 2025
ご来場いただきありがとうございます！
"Departure" today!
コンコンコン、こんあずきー！
Kon-kon-kon, Kon-AZKi!
あ、みんな元気がいいですね。
Ah, everyone's so energetic.
右手にマイク、左手に地図。
Microphone in my right hand, map in my left.
あなたのハートをゼロゲッサー、AZKiです！
The GeoGuessr of your heart, I'm AZKi!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure you enjoy the live show to the end, I have a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, recording, and the use of video equipment are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。喫煙はご遠慮ください。
Smoking is prohibited inside the building. Please refrain from smoking.
万一具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせず、近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
If you start to feel unwell, don't overexert yourself and notify a staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、
Activities such as moshing, diving, or throwing objects onto the stage,
他の皆さんの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
which may disturb others or hinder the show, are strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってください！
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
えらい！
Good job!
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが
Also, please note that cameras for video streaming and photography
会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合があります。
are in the venue, and the audience may be filmed.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに
Please be aware that these videos and photos may be used
使用される可能性がありますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
for promotional purposes.
はい！えらい！
Okay! Good job!
また、ライブのハッシュタグは「#AZKiと未来へ」です。
The hashtag for the concert is #AZKiToTheFuture (#AZKiと未来へ).
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてくれると嬉しい。お願いします！
I'd be happy if you used the hashtag to cheer us on. Please do!
それでは、開演までもう少しです。
Well then, it's almost time to start.
みんなの声、いっぱい聞かせてね！
Let me hear your voices!
Departure
もっと...
More...
もっと... ああ...
More... Ah...
鏡よ教えて
Mirror, mirror, please tell me
私のあした
About my tomorrow
...私は どこにあるのだろう
...where could I be?
分からない 分からないよ
I don't know, I just don't know.
周りと比べたってさ 虚しくなるだけ
Even if I compare myself to others, it only makes me feel empty.
あのノイズが海鳴りのように涙を奪う
That noise steals my tears like the roar of the sea.
切り取った風景を道標にしよう そうだ
I'll make this captured scenery my guidepost. That's right.
傷付いた感情も全て連れて行くから
Because I'm taking all my wounded emotions with me.
そっと響くカンパネラ 新しい未来を感じてる
A softly echoing campanella, I feel a new future.
怖くたって進むしかないでしょう 遠くまで
Even if I'm afraid, I have no choice but to move forward, far away.
届けこの祈りよ光となれ
Reach out, may this prayer become light.
もっと もっと 少しずつでもいい 私という答えを
More and more, even if just a little bit, the answer that is me.
もっと もっと
More and more.
嘘だよ 教えて
It's a lie, tell me.
私の 私は
My... who am I?
輝けるのかな 見つけたい 見つけたいよ
I wonder if I can shine. I want to find it, I really do.
誰かの決めつける輪 苦しくなるだけ
The circles defined by others only make things painful.
眠い目も力に変えるよ 心に誓う
I'll turn even my sleepy eyes into strength, I swear to my heart.
錆び付いた運命の歯車を回そう ほら
Let's turn the rusted gears of fate. Look.
着飾った感情は脱ぎ捨ててるから
Because I'm throwing away my dressed-up emotions.
そっと紡ぐフィロソフィ 叶えたい願いを信じてる
A softly woven philosophy, I believe in the wish I want to come true.
胸を張って歌うしかないでしょう 全力で
I have no choice but to sing with my head held high, with all my might.
欠片的な歌に変わる日まで
Until the day it turns into a song of fragments.
もっと もっと 嘆きながらでいい 全てが宝物
More and more, it's okay to grieve, everything is a treasure.
もっと もっと
More and more.
ぴあアリーナ！ 今日は楽しんでいってねー！
Pia Arena! Please enjoy yourselves today!
いつも近くこの声を 受け取ってくれたなら
If you've always received this voice near you...
この言葉を君に もう大丈夫 ひとりじゃない
I give these words to you: it's okay now, you're not alone.
強い想いを 繋ぐよ
I'll connect my strong feelings.
一歩踏み出してみた 優しく世界は微笑む
I tried taking a step forward, and the world smiles kindly.
高鳴る気持ちに身を任せて さあゆこう
Surrendering myself to these racing feelings, let's go.
そっと響くカンパネラ 新しい未来を感じてる
A softly echoing campanella, I feel a new future.
怖くたって進むしかないでしょう 遠くまで
Even if I'm afraid, I have no choice but to move forward, far away.
届けこの祈りよ光となれ
Reach out, may this prayer become light.
もっと もっと 少しずつでもいい 私という答えを
More and more, even if just a little bit, the answer that is me.
もっと もっと
More and more.
この扉の向こう側が 未知の可能性なら
If what lies beyond this door is unknown possibility...
今 動かせるの
I can move it now.
暗闇を手探りで 不安と焦燥の中
Groping through the darkness, amidst anxiety and frustration...
こぼれる光を見た
I saw a spill of light.
手を伸ばして
Reaching out.
la la la...
遠きを請ふて
Asking for the distant...
繋がるよ 心がいま
Connecting our hearts right now.
想像するの 私のストーリー
I'll imagine my story.
声を聞かせて 君を知りたいから
Let me hear your voice, because I want to know you.
輝かせよう 新しい世界
Let's make it shine, this new world.
生まれてきた意味を見つけるさ
I'll find the meaning of being born.
すべてが始まる この場所で
Everything begins in this place.
声が枯れるまで 叫んで
Shouting until my voice runs dry.
答え教えてよ 深夜のメランコリー
Tell me the answer, midnight melancholy.
イェーイ！
Yeah!
体と感情が 交差する
Body and emotions intersect.
正しい 自分は何？
What is the correct 'me'?
二途三途を繋いで 交差する
Connecting two paths and three paths, they intersect.
世界は 一つじゃない
The world is not just one.
インエクトファクタの数字 増えていく
The numbers of the infect factor are increasing.
盲目に正論 振りかざして 首を絞める
Blindly brandishing sound arguments, strangling me.
私の生きる世界は
Let me choose the world I live in
自分の手で選ばせてよ
with my own hands.
真夜中のメランコリー 生まれ変わるアイデンティティ
Midnight melancholy, a reborn identity.
この身が この辺が 痛いよ
This body, around here, it hurts.
上辺っ面のなきストーリー 執着してく可愛いフェイス
A story without superficiality, an obsessively cute face.
私は 私は 誰かにとって
I am, I am, for someone,
変わるの
changing.
どんどんいくよ！みんな手拍子お願いします！
Let's keep going! Everyone, please clap along!
どうして 気付いてしまったの
Why did I end up noticing?
熱くなるほどに
As it gets hotter and hotter...
隠しきれない 戸惑い
A bewilderment I can't hide,
ぎこちない距離 あやふやな姿勢
an awkward distance, an uncertain posture,
揺れる心 バレないように
so my wavering heart won't be found out.
人知れず 響く胸の鼓動
Secretly, my heart's drumbeat echoes.
口に出せば ままならないのに
Even though it won't go as I wish if I speak it aloud...
きっとどこかで 願っているんだ
Surely, somewhere, I am wishing for it.
終わりのない時間を
A time that never ends.
恋の始まりは 誰も知らない
No one knows the beginning of love.
私だけの 宝物
My own private treasure.
少しでも 言葉になりだしたら
If it even just slightly started becoming words,
もしも一つだけ 叶うのならば
If just one wish could come true,
ただ君のすぐ隣で
it would be to simply stay right by your side,
過ぎてゆく季節 眺めていたい
watching the passing seasons.
二人の声が 空に 吸い込まれていく
Our two voices are being sucked into the sky.
閉ざした世界 かすかに聞こえる音
A closed world, a faintly audible sound.
狭い部屋 二人 切り取って
In a small room, cutting out the two of us.
届きそうな手 すれ違った鼓動が
Hands almost touching, passing heartbeats,
ちょっと弾んだ
bounced a little.
ここで待って ここで待って
Wait here, wait here,
ここで待って 決められないままで
wait here, still unable to decide.
戸惑い溢れてしまうよ
My confusion is going to overflow.
もう何度も 繰り返した
I've already repeated it so many times.
こぼれた思いを数えて
Counting the spilled thoughts
何度も繰り返した
Repeated many times
世界 世界
World, World
日向を待っている
Waiting for the sunlight
まだまだ盛り上がっていくよ！
We're still going to get more fired up!
もっと声出せるよね！
You can shout louder, right?!
馬鹿馬鹿しいな 不自由な思考
How foolish, these restricted thoughts
意味がないなら 楽しい歌を
If there's no meaning, then a fun song
責めてる人 逃げてる人
The people accusing, the people running away
良くない人に 生きる力はない
Bad people have no power to live
舞え
Dance
前向きな夢
Positive dreams
狂った世界で僕らはみんな生きてるから
Because we're all living in this crazy world
好きになったりどうにかしちゃう 気取りの様に
Falling in love or doing something about it, as if posing
ニュースが流れた大事件に涙を流す人はいない
There's no one who sheds tears at major news incidents
びびるジェンガが嘘の街 さあ
The jittery Jenga is the city of lies, now
抜け出して
Escape
光の街へ
To the city of light
メドレーラスト！セイ ヘイヘイヘイ！
Medley's last! Say hey hey hey!
見せもんばかりすべて 上べで飾って誤魔化して
Everything is just a show, decorated on the surface to deceive
何が善悪か分からないから壊れていく
I don't know what's right or wrong, so it's breaking
一体何が本当なんだっけ
What on earth was real again?
期待しても何もなくて バカだいつも泣いて心配するよ
Even if I expect something, there's nothing, I'm an idiot, always crying and worrying
こんな異常だらけの世界で存在意義探してるんだ
In this world full of abnormalities, I'm searching for the meaning of existence
絶望のない自由なエリア どこですか？
Where is the hopeless, free area?
こんな異常だらけの世界で存在意義探してるんだ
In this world full of abnormalities, I'm searching for the meaning of existence
何を言われても満たされることないよ
No matter what anyone says, I'll never be satisfied
輝き連れて
Bring the sparkle
全て忘れて
Forget everything
はい！ということで、
Yes! So,
AZKi SOLO LIVE 2025 "Departure" へようこそー！
Welcome to AZKi SOLO LIVE 2025 "Departure"!
ちょっとぶっ飛ばしすぎた... ぶっ飛ばしすぎました。
I went a bit too fast... went too fast.
見渡す限り開拓者！
Pioneers as far as the eye can see!
本当に、もうこの景色を見て感極まってしまっているんですが、
Truly, looking at this scenery makes me so emotional,
みんな本当に今日来てくれてありがとうございます！
everyone, thank you so much for coming today!
今日は、AZKiにとって初めてのアリーナでのソロライブです。
Today is AZKi's first solo live in an arena.
この景色、本当にもう胸がいっぱいで... まだ早いか。まだ早いか、この辺は。
This view, my heart is really full... It's still too early. Still too early for this.
ということで、みんな今日はね、貴重な一日をこのAZKiのライブのために時間作ってくれてありがとうございます。
So, everyone today, thank you for taking time out of your precious day for this AZKi live.
早速なんですが、ぶっ飛ばしましたね、メドレー、どうでした？
Straight to it, we went fast, didn't we? How was the medley?
ありがとうございます。そしてね、もちろん一曲目はこの曲と決めていました。
Thank you. And of course, I decided the first song would be this one.
「未来カンパネラ」。ということで、新EPから、えーと「Restart」からね、一曲目をお届けしましたが。
"Mirai Campanella". So, from the new EP, um, from "Restart", I delivered the first song.
みんなEPは聴いてくれましたかー？
Did everyone listen to the EP?!
ありがとうございます。そしてそして、本日の衣装、どうですか？いいですかー？
Thank you. And then, how about today's costume? Is it good?!
早速ね、あのキービジュアルでみんなこの衣装来るんじゃないかと思ってたと思うんですけど。
Right away, I think everyone thought this costume would come based on the key visual.
なんと、初期のAZKiの...
Surprisingly, early AZKi's...
イメージして黒のカラーバリエーションも作っていただきました。
I also had them make a black color variation based on that image.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
そして今日の素敵なステージでございます。
And this is today's wonderful stage.
みんな上部の装飾気づきました？
Did everyone notice the decorations at the top?
変化してたの気づきました？この上のね、
Did you notice they were changing? These ones up here...
この今アルファっていう…
the ones that say "Alpha" now...
ほう、お、ピカピカピカ。ピカピカピカ。ありがとうございます。
Oh, they're sparkling! Sparkling! Thank you very much.
この変化気づきましたでしょうか。
I wonder if you noticed this change.
曲の頭で実はあの、このアルファの装飾部分がですね、
At the beginning of the song, the "Alpha" decoration part actually...
色が変わってまして、
the colors were changing,
みんなちょっとあの、続いて、これ大変だったよね。
everyone followed along, that must have been tough!
この色にしてください、っていうペンライトカラーになっておりました。
It became a penlight color that said, "Please use this color."
本当に曲の冒頭のほうなので、あの、見れた方は、
It was really at the very beginning of the song, so if you saw it...
ありがとう。あの、変えていただけたらなと思います。
Thank you. I hope you were able to change your colors.
それに合わせてね、みんなもペンライト点灯していただいたり、
Along with that, everyone lit up their penlights,
2色光ったときはですね、
and when two colors flashed...
ペンライトも2色にしてくださーい！
please change your penlights to two colors!
みんなで一緒に今日のライブ作ってこー、
Let's create today's live together!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you for your support!
ということで、今日のライブはですね、
So, today's live is...
バンドメンバーと一緒にお届けしてあります！
being brought to you together with the band members!
すごい、素晴らしい演奏ありがとうございます。
Wow, thank you for the wonderful performance.
しかもなんと、今回はですね、バイオリンも参加しております！
And what's more, this time we have a violin joining us too!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
今日の日のために、特別にアレンジした楽曲もたくさんあるので、
We have many songs specially arranged just for today,
お楽しみにー！
so please look forward to it!
そして今日はね、現地のみんなだけじゃなくてですね、
And today, it's not just everyone here at the venue...
配信で見ている開拓者もいます！
there are also Pioneers watching the livestream!
配信のみんなー！
Hello to everyone on the stream!
はい、コメントも見えてる。うおー、いぇー！
Yes, I can see your comments too. Whoa, yeah!
あずきちー！ふー、いぇー！アイオーリングがすごい。
Azukichi-! Phew, yeah! The I/O rings are amazing.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
ということで、本日はですね、
So, today...
ハッシュタグ、あずきと未来へ、で
using the hashtag #AZKiと未来へ,
今日の感想や印象に残った瞬間をポストしてください。
please post your thoughts on today's show and your favorite moments.
後で全部見に行きます！よろしくお願いします。
I'll go check them all later! Thank you in advance.
配信のみんなスクショもよろしく。
Everyone on the stream, please take screenshots too.
そして皆様、YouTubeやTikTokでご覧の皆様、
And to everyone watching on YouTube and TikTok,
残念ながら… お、早い、早い、早い。
unfortunately... Oh, that was fast, fast, fast.
無料チラ見せはここまでー！
the free sneak peek ends here!
ありがとうございます。現地の「えー」もいただきまして。
Thank you. I even got a "Eh-" from the venue.
まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたいみんなは、
For those who want to keep getting hyped with us,
概要欄のリンクから配信サイトへ飛べますので、
you can go to the streaming site via the link in the description.
ここからが本番なので、
The main show starts from here,
たくさんの人に見ていただきたいなと思っています。
so I hope many of you will watch.
今回のライブなんですが、これまでAZKiが歩んできた軌跡、
For this live, the path AZKi has walked so far,
そしてこれから歩んでいく未来、
and the future she will walk towards...
そのすべてをみんなと一緒にひとつの物語として、
I want to make today a day where we connect it all together
繋いでいくような一日にしたいと思っています。
with everyone as a single story.
このライブで、私の今のすべてを音楽とともに、
In this live, I will deliver my everything right now,
まっすぐみんなに届けていきます。
along with the music, straight to all of you.
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you for your support!
それじゃ、どんどん行きますよ！
Well then, let's keep going!
最後まで一緒に楽しんでいこうねー！
Let's enjoy ourselves together until the very end!
一緒に歌おー！
Let's sing together!
みんなの声聴かせて！
Let me hear your voices!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!
The free part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!